# Bryan Schneller

# Full-Stack Web Developer

730 Branniff Dr.
Cary, NC 27513
(484) 894-4578
bryan.schneller@gmail.com
https://bryanschnellerwebdev.netlify.app/

# **OVERVIEW**

I am an efficient and creative programmer with a strong vision for marketable product development. I am motivated to bring my talents and interests to contribute to a dynamic team. Eight years of experience in the brain injury rehabilitation field have strengthened my organizational, communication, and interpersonal skills. I enjoy the consistent challenge and considerable rewards of contributing to the internet which I regard as a fascinating achievement of humankind.

#### **SKILLS**

I have experience building unique and effective full-stack web applications using HTML CSS and JS, React.js, Node.js, Express.js, MongoDB and Mongoose, PostGreSQL and Sequelize, and using Git and Github and the agile framework in a team project development setting.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Wegmans, Cary, NC - Cashier (part-time)

AUG 2023 - PRESENT

- Provide a positive customer experience with thoughtful, individualized service
- Dynamically organize items for efficient and optimal bagging while handling cash transactions

Community Partnerships, Inc., Raleigh, NC - Rehabilitation Specialist

OCT 2022 - JUNE 2023

- Administered formal and informal assessments to create a treatment plan in order to prepare individuals for employment and independence
- Implemented person-centered treatment plans and carried out therapy sessions to address needs relating to cognitive rehabilitation, therapy and counseling, case management, and occupational preparation
- Schedule sessions and create plans to track and report treatment outcomes

Success Rehabilitation, Inc., Quakertown, PA - Cognitive Rehabilitation Specialist

FEB 2017 - SEPT 2022

- Administered standardized assessments and evaluations to determine individual strengths, weaknesses, and potential strategies
- Developed and implemented individualized treatment programs to address identified needs

 Functioned as on-call administrator to address staffing and maintenance issues and perform company-wide communications as needed

# **EDUCATION**

**University of Pittsburgh, PA** - Bachelor's of Science, Psychology (Cum Laude) SEP 2009 - MAY 2013

Solid academic foundation in the study of psychology including research methods, and biological, cognitive, and neuroscience aspects

# UNC Full-Stack Web Development Course, Chapel Hill, NC

NOV 2023 - May 2024

Accelerated program focused on independent coding and team project-management skills in technologies including HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, Express.js, Handlebars, React, Node.js, SQL and NoSQL databases, MERN stack, Git, Github, and the Agile development framework